Okay, then again.
Yes, er, I would like to play the game myself. I look forward to working with you.
Pleasure to meet you.
If we all, you know, try it here.
First things first.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
All right, let's get started!
This is a bit more than just a costume for the local club.
It's dark and elegant at the same time.
I think it's amazing.
When I was in middle school, if I had this on, I wouldn't have talked to you for a long time.
I was so excited.
I wore it to school.
You still talk to me the moment you put it on.
If someone tries to take a picture...
Here you go.
Here it is.
Okay, okay.
please.
I can see how I want to present myself and the atmosphere I want to create.
It's fun, isn't it?
What kind of maniacs are you?
I'm a jasmine tea fanatic.
I love jasmine tea so much!
I have a model of buying it at home in cardboard boxes.
I love jasmine tea.
I like jasmine tea.
Okay, here I go!
Yes, thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
What?
It was on the top of the grid.
Butterflies are the main focus of this music video.
I wonder who the butterfly will go to...
I think it would be an interesting music video if you look at it as if there is some kind of story.
I think it's going to be an interesting music video.
I will do my best today.
What kind of fanatic are you, Mr. Mototaka?
Gunpla...
I guess plastic models.
Yes, I make them.
And paint them.
I like to make them shine.
I like to make it shine.
Thank you very much.
He's so handsome.
He's so cool.
Thank you very much.
The overall length is...
It's amazing.
I haven't seen you guys.
How are you guys doing?
Good. - Good.
You know, when we're filming like this.
I'm like, "This would be better.
I love that feeling of building on top of each other to make something better.
I really love that.
But the live performance...
It's only one time, right?
I love that too.
That's great!
I'll be there.
Please do.
Yes, I'll be there.
Yay!
Yes, I'm going.
Can I have that smiley face?
A big smile.
How's that? How's that?
Oh, my God.
Okay, let's have a little bit of this.
I love it!
I've never bitten into a whole apple before, so it was a bit of a new experience for me.
I've never bitten into a whole apple before, so it was a new experience for me, but I tried it and it was surprisingly soft and tasty.
I'm a ramen maniac. I also walk around the room and make my own ramen.
I'm a ramen maniac!
How do you like this match?
I don't know, it's hard to see the game when you can change to queens, but I didn't see it from your stock.
I wish I was a prefect, I'd be in that exotic short room all the way down to the train station.
I'm gonna be staring at you.
Hey...
Winterize!
Oh, this is such a country! Three sheriffs, that's all!
It's always been like this
Abe, car imports...
me
I've been here.
Congratulations!
Congratulations
Yes, I'll cut it.
Thank you.
All seven members.
Surprisingly.
I hate to lose
I don't know...
like this
I love the members
but
But somewhere along the way
I have to win here.
I don't want to lose.
Even in performance
I think we can have friendly competition.
I think that's the value of our relationship.
I think we can have that kind of relationship.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
One, two, three...
Look, stop the diarrhea.
Six. Seven. Eight.
Four.
And then...
Face, not the front.
Look at the side.
Is that what you mean?
Then smile a little.
Laugh.
Like, "Han, Han.
You were saying.
Han. Han.
Han.
Like, with a mean streak.
Han. Han.
"Hang.
Pinky finger hurts.
Please.
Han. Han.
I'll say it for your little finger.
Where do you want me to fly?
Where are you going to fly?
I don't know...
I feel like I'm your source
This time it's really different from before
The taste is completely different from the past.
I wanted to do what I really wanted to do.
I wanted to make the best music video I could and leave it behind.
I'm thinking of doing it.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm going to work hard on the dance and other things
I'm going to do my best.
In the blink of an eye, the five of us will be grown up!
I know, it's fast, isn't it?
Just the two of us.
I guess we're all grown up now.
I want something.
I'd like to hear the music of the local section
I'd like to hear the music of the local club in even better sound quality.
What are those headphones called?
You mean you'll give them to me?
You're on your own.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Please do.
We were all talking about how we wanted to shoot something like this.
I'm so glad we got to do this for the first time.
I'm a fan of this stuff.
But I also like records.
I've been into R&B and shoegaze lately.
My brother recently got into music.
We often talk about it.
I think I like music.
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't know if it's because the members want to meet me.
Butterflies, some blue butterflies
It makes me look really cute.
It's not easy to find a costume with short pants.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm really looking forward to this new look.
So we're going to do our best!
Here it is.
This is awesome!
Ha-ha-ha!
I wonder what's in store for us.
Don't miss the show.
Don't say anything about the show.
I'm still listening.
Okay, we're done.
Okay, that's it.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
This is the full version.
This is full?
Left and a half.
Oh, I see.
So, one-quarter exchange.
Full size.
Oh, great.
If you could take a look at that.
Thank you very much.
You have a good eye.
I'm, uh...
I'm kind of a butterfly person.
Oh, I see.
How do butterflies fly?
He wants to know about butterfly life.
She wants to put wings on herself and fly.
and try to fly.
He was flapping his wings.
Like, "I'm a butterfly!
And then she did it in a kind of...
Like the Princess Kaguyahime.
I was doing it with a serious face.
So it's a kind of research, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm confident about the main part.
I've been doing a lot of muscle training lately.
My metabolism has gone through the roof.
Okay, I'll go in with Sempkin.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
I'm a maniac this time.
What kind of a maniac am I?
That's what I'm talking about!
Well, let me tell you what I am.
I am a natto maniac!
Especially, my mother makes a dish using natto.
She puts natto inside fried bean curd.
Natto wrapped in deep-fried tofu.
It's so delicious!
I love the taste and consistency of natto.
I love it!
I was talking about it a little bit, and I felt like eating it.
I'm going to ask my mother to make it for me.
What are you talking about?
Yes!
King corncobs!
No, thanks.
It's fine.
I'll seriously buy you something if you go before then.
That's a big round of applause.
Go, Kaname!
Don't stop now.
Go, go, go!
Chai chai.
Come on.
One.
In 10?
On 10?
Yes, sir.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
This is a craft reference.
I can't change this cool thing.
I can't change it.
Okay, here we go.
No smiles, please.
No smiles.
Thank you very much.
Yes, catto.
Thank you.
Please feel like we're staring at each other
Feel like yelling at the tree in front of you
Without a smile. Without a smile.
Without a smile.
Without a smile
When your hands are reflected
That's about as bad as it gets, really.
Well, that sucks.
What?
You make no mistakes when you're in the picture.
But when it's someone else's...
You know, my right hand is on top.
Oh, it's right. It's right.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Let me, let me, let me, let me, let me.
Diagonal, hmm, se, se
up, f-f-f, ja, ja, ja
ja, ja, ja, zu, gan
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you done?
I'm done.
Aim for the end.
Sick, sick, se, line.
One, two, three, four, five.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
16, 17, 18, 19.
please.
Yes, please.
Woh.
P.E.O.
See you soon.
Yes, please.
Funny.
Theme before the live show
Thank you
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am
yes
Thought vad
Kash
Kita
Katch
OECT
Honkou, no, thank you so much.
Good luck, good luck, good luck.
I did my best. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.